[SPEAKER_03]: I guess we'll start, let's get some of the housekeeping things out of the way first before we jump into actual hearings.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm gonna exercise chairman prerogative and we're gonna bat out of order a little bit.
[SPEAKER_03]: We'll still start off with the minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Daria, we're gonna call the meeting.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we'll start.
[SPEAKER_03]: So the first thing we wanna do is review the meeting minutes from the last meeting.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ben, Bob, you had a chance to look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I did look at it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number three is the only one that jumped to my attention and we're gonna resolve that today.
[SPEAKER_03]: But any comments or questions, anything on that?
[SPEAKER_03]: What was number three, Alan?
[SPEAKER_03]: It was regarding 61 Locust Street to Ford.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we had to table that because we wanted to see an advertisement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, that was what caught my attention.
[SPEAKER_04]: But I did think that that was what we had.
[SPEAKER_04]: said, I mean, it was a lot of minutes that are well put together, but I thought that was the only one I said, okay, that seemed like we were coming back to that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I didn't see an issue with it, but.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no, today we'll resolve all of that today.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that was the only thing on the minutes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bob, any questions for you?
[SPEAKER_02]: No, it all looked good to me, Alan.
[SPEAKER_02]: Just number three, I guess, was the only thing that we tabled.
[SPEAKER_02]: So we can discuss that today.
[SPEAKER_02]: It all looked good to me.
[SPEAKER_02]: I make a motion that we accept the minutes of the meeting from June 15th.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: I will second that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for that.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor, accepting the minutes for the last meeting, say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Motion carries, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's all set.
[SPEAKER_03]: That helps keeping things out of the way.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bistro five, I saw Vittorio, there he is.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vittorio, on my other screen I have Google Earth up of your establishment and the canopies and the tables are all still there on Google Earth.
[SPEAKER_03]: So if Google Earth says it's okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: It never left.
[SPEAKER_03]: So tell us, what are your plans?
[SPEAKER_03]: Is everything, are you staying in the same footprint?
[SPEAKER_03]: Give us a little map of what you're doing.
[SPEAKER_01]: So basically same exact as last year, but I'm not doing that whole wooden structure that I did last year, which was really nice, but it's just too much.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a lot to deal with.
[SPEAKER_01]: So I'm just gonna do what I did the year before, which was just basically the tables and the sidewalk,
[SPEAKER_01]: And then everything, you know, kind of like a little chain to kind of define the area, not chain, but like those little dividers, I guess.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, we have the Jersey barriers again, because like, like I said, on Google Earth, I can see the Jersey barriers.
[SPEAKER_03]: This just dropped off on Monday.
[SPEAKER_01]: They were dropped off on Monday, so we put up the sale.
[SPEAKER_01]: We're still there for a little bit of shade and just kind of to make it look a little bit interesting.
[SPEAKER_01]: But besides that, I'd say we're going to put some flowers around it this weekend and then put a few tables out and that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: Just for those people, we do have a few customers that are still masked up and still not comfortable.
[SPEAKER_01]: So it's nice to have that option, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: I wasn't going to do it, really.
[SPEAKER_01]: I didn't really want to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: but we got enough phone calls and- Yeah, no, I was surprised.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's, you know, we're midway through July, you know, and that's why I was wondering, you know, whether you were doing it or not, so.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, well, I really wasn't gonna do it, but then we did get enough phone calls and enough, and my staff was like, come on, they asked me to do it.
[SPEAKER_01]: I was like, if you guys wanna do it, let's do it then.
[SPEAKER_01]: Why not?
[SPEAKER_01]: It's a tough location, you know what I mean?
[SPEAKER_01]: Like between the train and the buses and, you know, the background noise is more often than not is FU.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: It's such an intersection, you know?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_01]: So, but I think we'll see.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we're keeping it simpler this year, so it should be okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ben, Bob, any questions?
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, Victoria is staying in the same footprint.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was success last time.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's just.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I've looked over it again and it was same as last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I think it's, yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I mean, it seems like it's a good option to have and I have no issues with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: And, you know, of course it's,
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I mean, right, it's just an option for you to have.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I have no problem with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no, I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, he's staying in the same footprint.
[SPEAKER_03]: He did it last year.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was no incidents, accidents, nothing.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just, why not?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's capture what's left of the summer outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: you probably have what 60 something days or 70 something days, whatever it is.
[SPEAKER_01]: I mean, if you just August and September, you know, I think it'll be, it'll be, it'll be good, good option.
[SPEAKER_01]: And you know, and who knows with these variants of a variant of a variant.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't have any other questions, especially where it's, we've, we've approved this before.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mr. Chairman, could I just clarify one thing if I may?
[SPEAKER_02]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_02]: Victoria, I wasn't here last year, but I believe I was in the area and I noticed that the tables are actually set up on the sidewalk with the Jersey barriers out in the street, primarily to not only protect your customers, but to protect the pedestrians that are walking in the street at that point going by your restaurant, correct?
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah, I just wanted to- The barriers, basically what the barriers do, they create a, basically the sidewalk continues onto the street and then it picks it up again after the patio, basically.
[SPEAKER_01]: It picks it right up again.
[SPEAKER_01]: So people just basically go around it and that's it.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's definitely been pretty safe.
[SPEAKER_01]: And it's never, you know,
[SPEAKER_01]: the ramp are all clear you know for wheelchair access and stuff those are all clear and we didn't really have any calls or complaints or anything last year so.
[SPEAKER_02]: No I noticed you did it last year and it was a nice job.
[SPEAKER_01]: Yeah I know I wish I could do that again but it was really a lot of work so it was a little too intense so we'll find something in the middle this year.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, but I mean, as far as the way the pedestrians walked it, it's pretty, you know, you've got a busy area around there and with the Jersey barriers, it's great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It not only protects, like I say, your customers, but the pedestrians.
[SPEAKER_02]: Definitely.
[SPEAKER_02]: You do a nice job with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: So yeah, I don't have a problem with any of this.
[SPEAKER_01]: Great, well, thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good, very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: One of you would like to make a motion?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'll make a motion to accept the alteration of premises for East Row 5
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll second the motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Uh, all in favor, say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It carries.
[SPEAKER_03]: Vittoria, good luck.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Hope all goes well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck, Vittoria.
[SPEAKER_01]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's, uh, jump into Winter Hill.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, there's nine of those.
[SPEAKER_03]: Um, Daria, are we good for that or no?
[SPEAKER_09]: We've got to get back daily on from winter Hill.
[SPEAKER_09]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: The camera was like looking at the wall and the ceiling.
[SPEAKER_03]: There you are.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_09]: Oh, am I on camera?
[SPEAKER_09]: I think I'm just on my mobile.
[SPEAKER_09]: I do have, uh, Maury Carol on as well.
[SPEAKER_09]: Who's going to help us, um, on one of the, uh, items on the docket specifically for, for the, uh, clipper ship data.
[SPEAKER_09]: this Saturday.
[SPEAKER_09]: The other eight items are for requests for one day permits associated with the yard beer garden that we ran this past spring, which we would love to do again this fall.
[SPEAKER_09]: But if possible, and I think Maury, you're on, if we could do the clipper ship event first, just
[SPEAKER_09]: so that Maury can drop.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no, I concur with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Maury, hi, good afternoon.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you for joining us.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you doing, everyone?
[SPEAKER_10]: Basically, what we're doing is what we do every year with the Chamber.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's Clippership Day, it's held on Clippership Drive, it goes from Parthia Way down to 99, that's all blocked off.
[SPEAKER_10]: The last few years that we've been running it, we've been doing a beer garden there.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have a 30 by 10 tent.
[SPEAKER_10]: It's all enclosed with the fencing and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: The beer garden is set up right next to the tent area.
[SPEAKER_10]: We also have Richie Slush in there and Colleen's.
[SPEAKER_10]: The mock moderato is the area is going to be doing cotton candy and so forth.
[SPEAKER_10]: So that's gonna be a little food and beer section down that end and the rest we have all the youth sports we have a dunk tank this year.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I mean it's a traditional clippership day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's a very successful where we are familiar with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: tell me um refresh my memory about the bear garden is that going to be in a contained area i know when we we did it in the upper square we had it in members plus their parking lot that was very nice because that was a very contained area or how tell us about how uh the plans for the for the area in the bear garden in the lower square it's it's it's the same as it has been we they have the um
[SPEAKER_10]: the metal fencing and they fence it off that way.
[SPEAKER_10]: The DPW does, I've already done the walkthrough with them regarding it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So, I mean, it's virtually all enclosed.
[SPEAKER_10]: Okay, so it's the same as the last time, all right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We'll be wristbanding folks who are of age as well.
[SPEAKER_04]: So they get wristbanded to go in the beer garden, and then the beer garden, that's the contained part.
[SPEAKER_04]: I didn't see it last year.
[SPEAKER_04]: I remember the event, but I didn't go to the event last year.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, that's the first thing, because it's kind of secluded.
[SPEAKER_10]: We tried to make that the first, so the only ones that are venturing into that area really are the ones that are consuming the beer and wine.
[SPEAKER_10]: I mean, the tent is really open for everyone, but with the access to the beer and wine service, it's only one way.
[SPEAKER_10]: make sense.
[SPEAKER_10]: We do have a police detail.
[SPEAKER_10]: Yeah, it's just a good, it's a good community event.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: We have to, as I said, we're all familiar with it.
[SPEAKER_03]: It is a great event.
[SPEAKER_03]: I guess, Dario, the insurance, do we have one on record or have you had, have they submitted one for the event?
[SPEAKER_03]: Maury, who's underwriting the insurance on it?
[SPEAKER_03]: I believe White the Hill's carrying all that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, correct.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, we should have, I believe we sent the COI in.
[SPEAKER_09]: So Daria, I think has it.
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't Daria, I can send it in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we have it for the record, just so we have a complete file and goes in the cabinet there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, what about police detail, Mario?
[SPEAKER_03]: We have 500 here.
[SPEAKER_03]: 500 unruly Metro residents, what do you think?
[SPEAKER_10]: We want about 1,200 to 1,300.
[SPEAKER_10]: That really makes for a good Metro crowd.
[SPEAKER_10]: But no, we have the police details.
[SPEAKER_10]: We have two officers on detail.
[SPEAKER_10]: And it's well contained.
[SPEAKER_10]: The pack of truck is there.
[SPEAKER_10]: There's no cars can get involved.
[SPEAKER_10]: And all the businesses in the square have been notified of it.
[SPEAKER_10]: So I mean, it's just four hours.
[SPEAKER_10]: City needs it bad.
[SPEAKER_10]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Well, I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ben, Bob, any questions?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: No questions from me.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like everything's in place.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, and he's got a good track record.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, it's been a successful event.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we can get a motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's get this one off the table.
[SPEAKER_02]: make a motion to grant the one day license for the, for the chamber event, Clippership Day.
[SPEAKER_04]: I second the motion for Clippership Day as well.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor of the one day license for Clippership Day say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: It carries.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Congrats.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope it's a success.
[SPEAKER_03]: I don't think there's rain on the,
[SPEAKER_03]: On the calendar, I know Tina's been doing her best to get me to be the guy in the dunk tank.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I said, no, I said, I don't need a bad back again.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I said, no, Tina, I'm not going to be the guy in the dunk tank.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brianna's jumping in.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is she?
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, wow.
[SPEAKER_04]: I just want to tell you, I just went in a dunk tank for my company and they put me in it since I'm the owner.
[SPEAKER_04]: And I must have gotten dunked five times and I was sore the next day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know if I'm going to dunk tank again.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've done my bit way back when, when we used to have, remember Maury, when you could pay to get someone arrested with the Keystone cops?
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember all of that?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jail day.
[SPEAKER_03]: Jail day it was.
[SPEAKER_03]: Remember jail day.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you, Mauri.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thanks, guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's one down and eight to go.
[SPEAKER_03]: Pete, you there?
[SPEAKER_03]: No?
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, Breck?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, I am still here.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So you wanna give us an overview of the eight?
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, so the eight, those represent three Saturdays in September and five in October.
[SPEAKER_09]: Our intent would be to run in the same exact program that we ran at the same location this past spring.
[SPEAKER_09]: I'm a family friendly block party.
[SPEAKER_09]: We ran from noon to right around seven o'clock.
[SPEAKER_09]: We had food, beer, wine, non-alcoholic beverages, and music.
[SPEAKER_09]: I think the reception was pretty good this spring.
[SPEAKER_09]: We took a break this summer just due to the heat.
[SPEAKER_09]: There's not a ton of shade in the parking lot.
[SPEAKER_09]: But our thought was we'd pick it up again this fall when it cooled down a little bit.
[SPEAKER_09]: So that first day is a week after Labor Day weekend, and we thought we'd
[SPEAKER_09]: we'd give it a run weekly on Saturdays until the end of October.
[SPEAKER_09]: In terms of logistics, it would be the exact same setup we ran this spring.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: And we have on record the insurance part.
[SPEAKER_03]: Are you going to submit that?
[SPEAKER_03]: And I think we have, Jerry, do we have a diagram or a plot that shows all of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do we have something from the last time, Dario?
[SPEAKER_09]: If you don't, I can reforward what we had put together last time, for sure.
[SPEAKER_04]: I actually remember seeing that, definitely, that diagram.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, we do.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's the same one, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, correct.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just think there should be one for every time there's a
[SPEAKER_03]: a request that should go in the file folder.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, so we've, you know, it looks complete.
[SPEAKER_03]: We've asked, we've asked, even though it's been in there a hundred times, maybe it's, maybe the simplest thing is for Dara to just pull it out of the other one and put it in that one.
[SPEAKER_03]: But I just want to make sure we have a complete package, so to speak.
[SPEAKER_03]: So we know that we've asked, you know, we're, we're just kind of asking for the same items over and over.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
Sure.
[SPEAKER_09]: Nope.
[SPEAKER_09]: No problem.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: So, so Breck, does that event happen?
[SPEAKER_04]: Do you guys run that event or are these just the dates that you're coming to that event?
[SPEAKER_09]: We, we ran the event.
[SPEAKER_09]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we, we, yeah, we, we, we do it ourselves.
[SPEAKER_09]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: And, um,
[SPEAKER_03]: Was this the one where we had some concerns about loud music, or was that another event?
[SPEAKER_09]: No, you are right.
[SPEAKER_09]: We did get one noise complaint on a day we had live music.
[SPEAKER_09]: I would say, admittedly, the band was a little bit on the loud side.
[SPEAKER_09]: So we, after that, I think only had live music one more time, and we just did it acoustic.
[SPEAKER_09]: I don't think we got any complaints the second time around.
[SPEAKER_09]: But you are correct, yeah, we did get a, we had a comment, one of the first ones, correct?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ben, Bob, any questions for the remaining eight one-day licenses?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know between these and the other set, because we only allow 30 in a calendar year,
[SPEAKER_03]: you know, we're not anywhere near it.
[SPEAKER_03]: I mean, as I said, back in the day, Springstep used to push the envelope with all the requests on calendar year.
[SPEAKER_03]: So how do you guys want to do it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you want to just do, just make a motion for all eight of them, the remaining eight, or individually, just... Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Mr. Chairman, can I ask a couple of questions?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Fire away.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, I know that we addressed the issue with the noise from the complaint we had at 6 Alfred Street, and that's great that they're addressing that.
[SPEAKER_02]: There's a couple of things I noticed.
[SPEAKER_02]: On the one day alcoholic beverage license applications, on page two of all of them,
[SPEAKER_02]: The month is not there for the date that it was signed.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure what it is.
[SPEAKER_02]: It was four boxes with Xs in them.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think if we just get a month, we could probably just fill it in ourselves for our records, because right now it's not showing the month.
[SPEAKER_09]: And- That may be a scanning issue on my end.
[SPEAKER_09]: I can update that and send those in at my call probably.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that'd be great.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's on page two where it says signed and subscribed to under the penalty and perjury this 23rd day of blank, blank, blank 2022.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, that was one of the questions I had.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the other one was, did you happen to notify the police department about a detail
[SPEAKER_02]: And if so, you know, if you may wanna just give them the dates that you're having it, so you only have to call them once.
[SPEAKER_02]: If they say, no, you don't need it, then it's done.
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, if they do say it, then, you know, you guys will be able to figure it into your expenses or whatever it may be if they are going to require it.
[SPEAKER_09]: Sure, and Daria sent me an email on that this morning, so I will submit that.
[SPEAKER_09]: that notification this afternoon.
[SPEAKER_02]: Other than that, good luck with it.
[SPEAKER_02]: It looks like a good time.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, Bobby, I was looking at that too, but doesn't it say it's the 23rd day of June, 2022?
[SPEAKER_04]: Doesn't that mean it's... Yeah, that's, I'm confused.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's like something is like blanked out, but I still think it reads correctly.
[SPEAKER_02]: Does it say June?
[SPEAKER_02]: Cause mine doesn't say June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: It says June.
[SPEAKER_04]: Maybe when it printed it missed June.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Mine says, mine says this 23rd day of June, 2022.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh, okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So it may be something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I was kind of, I was going to, I was going to ask you later on.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just, I wasn't following what you were pointing out.
[SPEAKER_03]: I kind of looked at the rest of them and they're all,
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all the same, they're all printed.
[SPEAKER_03]: At least on mine they printed out right.
[SPEAKER_02]: No, see mine didn't.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I'm sorry, my apologies.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's probably my printer.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm sorry, that's a good catch.
[SPEAKER_03]: So one of you want to make a motion?
[SPEAKER_03]: Let's tie the eight of them together?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I can do that.
[SPEAKER_04]: So provided that we have the insurance and then the diagram that we can file that, and I know the police detail has been
[SPEAKER_04]: is going to be taken care of.
[SPEAKER_04]: I would make a motion to approve the eight one-day liquor licenses for the events at the beer garden at 100 Winchester Street, Medford, the yard.
[SPEAKER_04]: And that's 9-10, 9-17, 9-24, 10-1, 10-8, 10-15,
[SPEAKER_04]: 1022, 1029.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_03]: 1022 and 1029, yep.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll second the motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor, except in the eight one-day licenses for Winter Hill Brewing, say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: It carries.
[SPEAKER_03]: They're all set.
[SPEAKER_03]: Brett, good luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: I hope no rain.
[SPEAKER_03]: No rain.
[SPEAKER_09]: Yeah, me too.
[SPEAKER_09]: Thank you very much.
[SPEAKER_09]: I appreciate you guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Number four, I have the Ford.
[SPEAKER_03]: I see the two of you there.
[SPEAKER_03]: How are you guys?
[SPEAKER_03]: Good to see you.
[SPEAKER_06]: Hi, Mr. Chair, Attorney Trish Farnsworth as well on behalf of the licensee.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I know this is a little deja vu, but we already had this full hearing.
[SPEAKER_06]: It was a change of manager and two owners, small owners, you know, are no longer with the company.
[SPEAKER_06]: So we were just notifying of that.
[SPEAKER_06]: And I think there's just a little confusion on whether that needed to be advertised to change of ownership.
[SPEAKER_06]: So what we did was advertise it, notify about it as the usual.
[SPEAKER_06]: And so now we're here today.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah, there's entertainment license to it said on the agenda.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah no Miss Farnsworth you're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_03]: We did that this the first time we were, we were perfectly fine with, with the application but we did want to take care of those two loose ends, and
[SPEAKER_03]: and Daria sent to us the ad, here it is here.
[SPEAKER_03]: We saw it, Bob, Ben, did you see, take a look at the ad there?
[SPEAKER_03]: I had to use my cheetahs, it's so freaking small, it's just, all I can say is don't turn 60, it's all downhill after 60.
[SPEAKER_03]: But yeah, no, thank you, thank you for doing this, thank you.
[SPEAKER_06]: So- No problem, and we actually have,
[SPEAKER_06]: you know, Barry Rafferty here, he couldn't attend last time.
[SPEAKER_06]: So he's the founder and he lives there in Medford.
[SPEAKER_06]: So I just wanted to point that out.
[SPEAKER_06]: He's here as well this time.
[SPEAKER_06]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: In that it goes to the minutes because that was one of the conditions we had asked for, uh, for the advertisement.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, so I'm perfectly fine with the, with that, that application, uh, Ben, Bob, any, any, any followup questions?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know we kind of,
[SPEAKER_03]: went through it the last time.
[SPEAKER_03]: I just wanna make sure you guys are satisfied now that they're advertised and we have a copy of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then let's jump over to the entertainment request.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'm all good with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Ben, what about yourself?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I'm all good.
[SPEAKER_04]: So that's for the change of manager part.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's the ad.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yep.
[SPEAKER_04]: I'm good with that too.
[SPEAKER_04]: I looked at it, I saw the ad and.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, because that was.
[SPEAKER_06]: Change of manager and change of ownership.
[SPEAKER_03]: Change of ownership interest.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: That's right.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that, Daria, did we make a motion and vote on it last time or do we just need to remove the condition, which was the ad?
[SPEAKER_12]: I think it's just to remove the condition that he needed it at.
[SPEAKER_12]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So Ben, Bob, if you want to just make a motion to accept that now that we've, we've seen the advertisement so we can get that off the table.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I'll make the motion just to accept that we've seen the ad and we can proceed with the change of ownership and management for the Ford.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: I second that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor of accepting the application for the change of management and ownership interest say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: So that's done.
[SPEAKER_03]: So let's jump over to the entertainment application.
[SPEAKER_03]: Do you guys got that part of it?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: So tell us, what are the plans?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know I keep hearing the word acoustic.
[SPEAKER_03]: So tell us, what are your entertainment plans besides
[SPEAKER_03]: music uh in your um the screens all the behind the bar and around the malls.
[SPEAKER_11]: Hey uh guys we can't hear you yeah yeah
[SPEAKER_06]: Just try again, Heath, I think you were not right up to the- Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_06]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_11]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: All right, so our plan for the music side of things was just to have acoustic one to three people top bands that are just kind of background music for our patio during our services.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not gonna be a ticketed type of anything.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's not gonna be events or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's more just kind of a background,
[SPEAKER_11]: something to add to our guest experience.
[SPEAKER_11]: That's all.
[SPEAKER_03]: Let me see.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_11]: It's me.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, I know we, as you heard from went to hell they had
[SPEAKER_03]: And then the noise complaint, but it doesn't sound like you're going to have any kind of a band like that you're just going to have some background music, especially where we are so close to all the apartment you know the apartment building there you know that we had.
[SPEAKER_03]: some concerns with the porch because the buildings were tall and the street was narrow and the music just carried right up into everyone's apartment.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I know it's not going to be anything like that.
[SPEAKER_03]: But so as long as you're telling us it's going to be kind of background music, acoustical background music, then I think we understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: In addition to music inside piped in, right?
[SPEAKER_03]: And then you got the flat panel screens mounted on the walls also, correct?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, seems oh yeah seems seems clear.
[SPEAKER_04]: Music doesn't sound like a problem.
[SPEAKER_04]: The porch, kind of, they took their concerts outside.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's a little different.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, same thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it was because of the COVID.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I'm, yeah, again, to me it's very straightforward.
[SPEAKER_03]: I've eaten at the establishment, it's great.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so, yeah, I think you got a nice setup there with the patio there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Did anybody go into that bank?
[SPEAKER_03]: There was like Easton Bank there or something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is that an empty building?
[SPEAKER_03]: Everything to the right is empty?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, yeah, okay.
[SPEAKER_08]: I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_08]: Ben, Bob, any?
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you hear me?
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry, just, we will do some sort of a background music, a singer or two singers on the patio.
[SPEAKER_08]: early evening.
[SPEAKER_08]: Barry, can you speak into the microphone?
[SPEAKER_08]: Yeah, you're breaking up.
[SPEAKER_08]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_08]: Can you hear me now?
[SPEAKER_07]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_07]: Sorry.
[SPEAKER_07]: We will look to do background music, live background music on occasion on the patio as well.
[SPEAKER_07]: But let's be clear, we're very cognizant of our neighbors.
[SPEAKER_07]: We invested heavily in all of our soundproofing underneath already.
[SPEAKER_07]: So to be honest, the guy who lives directly above us has said that he can't hear anything from downstairs.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we did a good job on that.
[SPEAKER_07]: But in relation to the patio, I think it'd be a lovely thing if you're out there having a brunch or an early evening meal, that there was a singer with, you know, no speakers or anything like that.
[SPEAKER_07]: It's all low key.
[SPEAKER_07]: Just, you know, just to have a little bit of background music and a bit of entertainment.
[SPEAKER_07]: So we will look to do that.
[SPEAKER_07]: So I wouldn't like to hide anything from you.
[SPEAKER_07]: But we are very aware of where we are and we will listen very carefully to anybody who has any adverse comments, which I don't think they will.
[SPEAKER_07]: I want you to be aware that we do plan to do that.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, I fully understood that you wanted to do inside and outside.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I guess you're absolutely right.
[SPEAKER_03]: As long as you're aware of the noise level and ultimately, if people are constantly complaining, then we'll have to revisit the whole thing.
[SPEAKER_03]: But again, I'm fine.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm glad that you are aware of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Anything from the other commissioners?
[SPEAKER_04]: That's how I understood it as well, so no.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have any other questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good.
[SPEAKER_02]: It sounds like you're doing it up right.
[SPEAKER_02]: I don't have a problem with it at all.
[SPEAKER_02]: Congratulations.
[SPEAKER_02]: Good luck with it.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, so let's make a motion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Let's get this off the table.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I will make a motion to accept the entertainment license for the Ford for, yeah, 61 local street.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, that's, well, I'm sorry, for Mystic Dining LLC, so, Ford Tavern.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'll second the motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good, yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: I used to say, all in favor and seeing none, I think is what he used to say all the time.
[SPEAKER_04]: Hearing none.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: The entertainment license has been approved.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good luck guys.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_06]: Thank you for your time.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_03]: The last item is Ocean State Job Lot.
[SPEAKER_03]: Ben and Bob, did you get the last package?
[SPEAKER_03]: I know Daria was sending out the package.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's gonna come under any and all other business that may arise.
[SPEAKER_03]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bob?
[SPEAKER_03]: I got it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Elizabeth, how are you?
[SPEAKER_05]: Hi, thank you for
[SPEAKER_05]: having me today.
[SPEAKER_05]: Elizabeth Blank, Corporate Counsel, Ocean State Job Lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: Basically, here with our management agreement on behalf of the licensee, OSJL Spirits LLC, really what the management agreement is doing is we're looking to leverage the resources of the parent company of Ocean State Jobbers in terms of
[SPEAKER_05]: you know, HR department, payroll, marketing, et cetera, and to more efficiently run our store operations for the just handful of Massachusetts stores that we have with beer and wine licenses.
[SPEAKER_05]: So right now, that's currently eight, of which Medford is one.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as you may know, Ocean State Jobbers maintains the premises as a general retail store.
[SPEAKER_05]: So as far as we have the licenses in the other few locations, we look to use this corporate expertise to make our alcohol sales portion of the retail operations more streamlined while continuing to maintain a high quality of operations and using our high quality employees.
[SPEAKER_05]: OSJL Spirits LLC does not have a history of disciplinary actions.
[SPEAKER_05]: And as such, Ocean State Jobbers seeks to continue to maintain the high level of operational standards that are already in place.
[SPEAKER_05]: The management fee is outlined in the management agreement.
[SPEAKER_05]: It's a combination of fair market value of expenses incurred
[SPEAKER_05]: an additional percentage of net profits, any additional fees and expenses and considerations if the parties agree or do an owing to Ocean State Jobber's performance of the services.
[SPEAKER_05]: Ocean State Jobber's as a manager would maintain the liquor liability insurance and make sure the taxes are paid and up to date and really just ensuring compliance overall.
[SPEAKER_05]: But OSJL Spirit LLC as a licensee would main control
[SPEAKER_05]: maintain control over the accounts, ability to audit the accounts, effective control of the assets, and all title to alcohol and licenses.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are there any questions that I could answer?
[SPEAKER_04]: I have a question.
[SPEAKER_04]: You said there were no issues.
[SPEAKER_04]: Wasn't there an issue of some of the liquor being expired that was getting sold a couple of years ago?
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, about a year and a half ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: That is pending.
[SPEAKER_05]: That hearing happened, I believe, two months ago.
[SPEAKER_05]: So there's no outcome on that for OSJL Spirits LLC.
[SPEAKER_05]: Are there any other pending things?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, not that I'm aware of.
[SPEAKER_05]: OK.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bob, did you have a question?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: Elizabeth, on page 7, under Entity Vote,
[SPEAKER_02]: I noticed on the top line that says the board of directors are LLC managers of supposed to be the entity name, it was left blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: And it continues to read, duly voted to apply to the licensing authority of Medford and the Commonwealth of Massachusetts ABCC on date of the meeting, which I would imagine is today.
[SPEAKER_02]: but there's nothing in that entity name.
[SPEAKER_02]: Would we be able to put something in there that's supposed to be?
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes, page seven of... Entity vote, I think is that page, Bob?
[SPEAKER_11]: Entity vote, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Entity vote, yeah.
[SPEAKER_11]: At the top.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the attachment, it was page seven.
[SPEAKER_02]: I'm not sure if it was technically seventh location.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh yeah, it's blank there.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, it's after the additional information page.
[SPEAKER_03]: Oh.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's actually where Robert signed and... Yes, I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Yes, I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Okay, so the date of meeting is what's missing, is what you're indicating.
[SPEAKER_02]: In the first one, the entity name.
[SPEAKER_05]: Oh, that's odd, because it's, I have it on my copy.
[SPEAKER_05]: This was submitted by outside council.
[SPEAKER_05]: It says OSJ comma LLC DBA Ocean State Job Lot.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can do that.
[SPEAKER_05]: I'll provide you with that.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, mine's blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: So, Attorney Blank, if you could send us another version, yeah, that would be great.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_02]: I didn't know if it was my printer playing tricks on me.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, not this time.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, me too, it's blank.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the date of meeting would be today, correct?
[SPEAKER_00]: Correct.
[SPEAKER_05]: I will get that to you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you for pointing that out.
[SPEAKER_05]: I think there was an issue with the first set of documents that came over were only scanned on one side.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm not sure what the second version looked like because the management agreement was actually double-sided.
[SPEAKER_05]: So.
[SPEAKER_04]: And now I'm just trying to remember there was a gentleman in and he was going to be the new manager.
[SPEAKER_04]: It was a couple of maybe a year ago or so.
[SPEAKER_04]: For store level?
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, maybe it was for store level.
[SPEAKER_04]: Solomon, Solomon, maybe level manager.
[SPEAKER_04]: There could, but don't, maybe Alan, you can remind me, was there some other kind of issue we had been discussing at that point with maybe carding or anything like that?
[SPEAKER_03]: No, no, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: There was something way back, you know, pre-COVID, it might as well be even the dinosaurs.
[SPEAKER_03]: It was just, I think it was something to do with,
[SPEAKER_03]: I think it was a cashier that was, you know, selling, wasn't checking IDs and they took the proper steps to, you know, correct the issues and make sure incidents like that don't happen again.
[SPEAKER_03]: But that was the only other time other than what you were referring to.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: I think they've been,
[SPEAKER_03]: You know, Ocean State has been a very good corporate neighbor of the community.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's only been one incident since we've, you know, we've done, you know, with them, so.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, I think that's probably what's going in, floating in the back of your mind, that one incident back then.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: No, and I haven't heard anything since.
[SPEAKER_04]: That's what is that being looked into.
[SPEAKER_05]: Um, well we had the hearing and you are probably well aware that ABCC is moving at a very slow pace so they said, I don't know, maybe even 12 months to hear back about.
[SPEAKER_05]: what the outcome is on that.
[SPEAKER_05]: So I'm sorry if it came off as I misspoke on that, that I was talking about specifically to, or in my mind thinking specifically of the Medway location, but this is the only other issue as you indicated about the Sangria, I believe.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, no, it's fine.
[SPEAKER_04]: It just seemed like you're reading like a statement or something and there were some things.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, yeah.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay, I think that well, that's seems like everything's being addressed.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I don't have any further questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah, no.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just some minor things in there and in the attorney will get us a revised copy of it.
[SPEAKER_03]: So I don't have any questions.
[SPEAKER_03]: So one of you, if not, yeah, then make a motion.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, I would make a motion just to get the wording right.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's the minute.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's a new MIT.
[SPEAKER_04]: So it's an application.
[SPEAKER_04]: It's an amended management agreement, Alan.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: Amended management agreement.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Application for amended management agreement.
[SPEAKER_04]: Say that five times fast.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_04]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_04]: So I will make a motion to accept the application for the amended management agreement for Ocean State Job Lot as was just presented to us by Elizabeth Blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: With the revised version.
[SPEAKER_04]: Yeah, including the entity's name on page seven.
[SPEAKER_11]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: Give me a second.
[SPEAKER_12]: I did find something.
[SPEAKER_03]: Attorney Blank, is that something that you can just PDF to us now or no?
[SPEAKER_05]: No, I need to get it from outside counsel.
[SPEAKER_05]: I see.
[SPEAKER_05]: Because they generated the document.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_05]: But I can ask that they send it over.
[SPEAKER_03]: To Daria, please.
[SPEAKER_12]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: No luck, Daria.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on, I'm just trying to open it.
[SPEAKER_12]: Hold on.
[SPEAKER_12]: I'll send it to you guys, but I think that's the same thing.
[SPEAKER_08]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Bob, you second the motion?
[SPEAKER_02]: Yes, I second the motion.
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor of accepting the amended management agreement application, say aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: Aye.
[SPEAKER_03]: All in favor?
[SPEAKER_03]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you very much, Attorney Blank.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate the narrative and we appreciate your time for helping
[SPEAKER_03]: helping us understand what's happening here.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_05]: I appreciate your time.
[SPEAKER_05]: Have a great rest of your week.
[SPEAKER_03]: Thank you.
[SPEAKER_04]: Very good.
[SPEAKER_04]: Is school out for the summer, Mr. Matarado?
[SPEAKER_04]: I don't know.
[SPEAKER_02]: It's still early.
[SPEAKER_02]: Still early, yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: So tell us, tell us more.
[SPEAKER_03]: So where, so September we come back in person.
[SPEAKER_12]: Same question.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_12]: As far as I understand.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yes.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_03]: Is there anything percolating that you think we might have to get together and in August?
[SPEAKER_12]: I mean, this is all the stuff that I've gotten so far.
[SPEAKER_12]: So I tried to get everybody.
[SPEAKER_12]: in for this meeting so as far as we haven't received any other requests.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_12]: As of today at least.
[SPEAKER_12]: Well, let's say not today just now.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And so you'll follow up with the, with the, with the insurance.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: And the, the diagram or the design.
[SPEAKER_12]: Yeah, I didn't ask them for it.
[SPEAKER_12]: They just said that it was, I don't remember what Breck said, but I didn't ask for it.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_03]: No, we just want to get in the habit of asking everybody for them because remember we decided, you know, let's just ask everybody, let's request one all the time.
[SPEAKER_03]: It's just a good habit to get into so we're consistent.
[SPEAKER_03]: I agree.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Well, if there's no other questions.
[SPEAKER_02]: Was he going to get in touch with the police department area?
[SPEAKER_02]: Did he say he said, yeah, he did.
[SPEAKER_02]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: I think that was the only other thing.
[SPEAKER_02]: I did have an aerial shot of his property that I Googled when we got that complaint from the neighbor at 6 Alfred Street.
[SPEAKER_02]: And the neighbor's pretty close.
[SPEAKER_02]: He's like diagonally across from their parking lot.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I think if they're gonna do it without the amps and everything else, it's just acoustical and a little background music, I think they'll be fine.
[SPEAKER_02]: Because he even admitted that
[SPEAKER_02]: it was kind of loud so yeah yeah people all up in arms but uh there shouldn't be a problem and if there is i'm sure we're going to get a complaint and we can you know probably take care of it uh i mean we can amend well nothing really i don't know how you guys handle it if they don't abide by the rules as far as um
[SPEAKER_02]: You know, like if we if we give them a warning, hey, you got to tone it down and no more music or whatever.
[SPEAKER_02]: says.
[SPEAKER_03]: yeah we can cross that bridge but yeah there's nothing where it's eight licenses it goes all the way to our tall where we you're right, you know if if something.
[SPEAKER_03]: you know, arises, we can always address it and ask them to have a special meeting and have them come back and we can address it with them, you know, in a public forum.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sure, sure.
[SPEAKER_03]: I'm looking at Google Earth too.
[SPEAKER_03]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, I mean, they're cool.
[SPEAKER_02]: They're pretty professional.
[SPEAKER_02]: They seem to have everything in order every time they come before us, you know.
[SPEAKER_02]: So I don't think any issues.
[SPEAKER_03]: Good, good, good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well, if there's no other concerns, Dari, any concerns on your part, anything?
[SPEAKER_03]: Nothing, very good.
[SPEAKER_03]: Okay, well then let's call meeting adjourned at 1.55.
[SPEAKER_03]: I thank you commissioners for your time.
[SPEAKER_03]: We appreciate it.
[SPEAKER_03]: And then hopefully nothing comes up on the docket for next month and we have some time off when we get together in September.
[SPEAKER_03]: Sounds good.
[SPEAKER_02]: Sounds like a plan.
[SPEAKER_03]: All right, good.
[SPEAKER_02]: All right, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Yeah, thank you, guys.
[SPEAKER_02]: Thank you, Dario, as always.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye.
[SPEAKER_02]: Bye-bye.